All by my lonesome, I was powerless, and so
I really held no kind of value at all
Faced with that emptiness and drowning in it
I was always so anxious about tomorrow
And by some random chance, the people I met back then
Called me their friend without a second thought
So I realised something precious to me, deep in my heart
When it's for someone's sake, and for their sake alone,
Even a person like me can become a hero at any time
Two stories come together by this miracle
Almost as if someone from the future pulled the string of fate along
A single emotion transcends even space-time itself
A seemingly endless light traces the outline of the gate
Reminding me of the "Observer," perhaps I would want to say...