Drawn together into one by a mysterious force
Those days where everyone's hopes and dreams overlapped
We rushed straight down a path filled with sorrows and joys
Our Avant Story
Make no mistake, this is no coincidence―that is not even up for speculation
Nor is it an inevitability; it's just the aesthetic of self-righteousness
In a multi-dimensional composition, wielding falsehood as its sword
As if trying to provoke me, the sky is so deceiving
I am to the New World Order; what will the weather be?
God will come down to the world; a tempestuous storm
Wind is blowing from the northeast―the time limit is approaching
Once again, for all the people that we've lost, we cannot back away anymore
There is something invisible tying past and future together
With a vigor one could only describe as "obsession"
Though the chances are minuscule, smaller than even cosmic dust,
You keep believing with those honest eyes of yours
And thus I vow to protect this baton