Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪ Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪
Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪ Da-li-da-li-ya-a-a♪
Tu Tu Ru La La La La♪
Hate is the opposite of love
But then, what is love the opposite of?
My train of thought is already coming to a stop
Well, whatever, it's not like I'm going out anyway
Even when nothing seems to be happening
Suddenly, radio waves start flying around
Beep beep beep
No way... Could this be the spark of love?
Wha-!?
Dance with me
Instead of worrying or making yourself sick,
You should just dance the night away (within reason)
So take my hand and step to the beat
If we laugh together, we win!
Dance with me
Just for a bit, let's overcome our forbidden love with multiplication
And then even times that should be boring
Will turn into happy, happy moments
Everybody now!
Aah~ Foo~↑
Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪ Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪
Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪ Da-li-da-li-ya-a-a♪
Oh man, now I really wanna dance too...
Frau-tan, c'mon!
Tu Tu Ru La La La La♪
You say hate is the opposite of love
But if we're not careful, there's tons of pitfalls to fall into
Once you get the fever, it's already too late
You'll forget to even eat and sleep
Times that are all too fun
Will pass way too fast, like in 2x speed
(sonic speed)
If you check your schedule, you'll notice you forgot all your plans
Ah!
You guessed it
Take all your failures and things that make you sad
Throw them all out and dance away (within reason)
Every time you feel my heart beating hard
It's because your love is growing
Dance with me
Just for a bit-it's fine if it's sudden-switch yourself from timid to attack mode
Let's take this world with nothing interesting to do
And turn it into a happy, happy place
Enako-chan, come dance with us!
Aah~
Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪ Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪
Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪ Da-li-da-li-ya-a-a♪
Tu Tu Ru La La La La♪
One more time!
Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪ Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪
Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪ Da-li-da-li-ya-a-a♪
Tu Tu Ru La La La La♪
Ah, I'm beat... this burnt way more
..calories than I thought it would.