Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪ Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪
Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪ Da-li-da-li-ya-a-a♪
Tu Tu Ru La La La La♪
Hate is the opposite of love
But then, what is love the opposite of?
My train of thought is already coming to a stop
Well, whatever, it's not like I'm going out anyway
Even when nothing seems to be happening
Suddenly, radio waves start flying around
Beep beep beep
No way... Could this be the spark of love?
Wha-?!
Dance with me
Instead of worrying or making yourself sick,
You should just dance the night away (within reason)
So take my hand and step to the beat
If we laugh together, we win!
Dance with me
Just for a bit, let's overcome our forbidden love with multiplication
And then even times that should be boring
Will turn into happy, happy moments
Let's turn them into happy, happy moments
Aah~ Foo~↑
Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪ Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪
Tu Tu Ru Tu Ru Tu♪ Da-li-da-li-ya-a-a♪
Tu Tu Ru La La La La♪