You know, your loud voice calling out to me—it moved me to my core
The smile you always wear is shining so bright
It makes the sky up above look so dazzling
It's true, we spent irreplaceable days with one another
Mornings filled with joy and evenings stained by sorrow, too;
They've all led up to this day
A moment that seems like a miracle rains down upon us right now
And within that light a rainbow will appear, representing our own dazzling hope
I feel that any dream and any wish, any future alike,
Will come true if I stay by your side
Even in the middle of darkness, I want to find the strength to carry on;
I want to seize it with this hand of mine
Even beyond the deepest depths of the universe,
Our overlapping feelings must be resounding all the same
Even as time comes and goes, I won't ever let go of the truth—
That we can still believe in each other